<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Konstantin Denerz</title>
    <link>https://konstantin-denerz.com/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Konstantin Denerz</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 20:00:00 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://konstantin-denerz.com/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Angular Material 3 Theming: Design Tokens and System Variables</title>
      <link>https://konstantin-denerz.com/angular-material-3-theming-design-tokens-and-system-variables/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 20:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://konstantin-denerz.com/angular-material-3-theming-design-tokens-and-system-variables/</guid>
      <description>If you work with Angular and don&amp;rsquo;t want to or can&amp;rsquo;t develop every single component yourself, you use a framework like Angular Material. One of the great things about the framework is that it is based on a modern design system, Google&amp;rsquo;s Material version 3, and supports design tokens. This provides every product/project team with a common foundation that Product Owners, designers, customers, and developers can work on together.
In this article, I describe how to implement a Material 3 theme using the Angular Material framework.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>View Transitions with Angular (SPA)</title>
      <link>https://konstantin-denerz.com/view-transitions-with-angular-spa/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Apr 2023 10:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://konstantin-denerz.com/view-transitions-with-angular-spa/</guid>
      <description>View transitions is a cool and powerful API we can use in our Angular application to create animated transitions between views to elevating the overall user experience and enhancing usability, resulting in positive user feedback.
Update [2023-09-12] Angular router now supports View Transitions. (#73e4bf2) Use Case The use case in this article is a single page application built with Angular to demonstrate a portfolio of a user. As in most customer projects, I also set up and use a design system here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello Friend</title>
      <link>https://konstantin-denerz.com/hello-friend/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2023 20:19:37 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://konstantin-denerz.com/hello-friend/</guid>
      <description>Hello and welcome to my blog! My name is Konstantin Denerz, and I&amp;rsquo;m a consultant, coach, and developer with over 20 years of experience in development on platforms like .NET, Java, and web. During this time, I have gained extensive experience in various technologies, frameworks, and tools. My current focus is on Angular and UX/UI design, and I&amp;rsquo;m passionate about sharing technical knowledge with others. Find more about me on the about me page.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
